Gerard P. Kuiper papers 1894-1992 (bulk 1949-1973)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VII: National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1954-1974.
  - Subseries 10: Manned Spacecraft Center
    - 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 11: Mariner Program Mars- Mercury-Venus (MMV)
    - Sub-subseries 1: General
      - 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Mariner 73 TV Experiment Team Reports
      - 1970 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - 1971(1) (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - 1971(2) (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - 1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Photographs taken by Mariner Program
      - 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Mariner 9 - Photographs
      - 1972 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Mariner study meeting
      - 1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 12: NASA Missions Loose Handwritten Notes by Dr. Kuiper
    - undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 13: NASA University Program Review Conference
    - 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 14: NASA Office of University Affairs
    - 1966-1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 15: NASA Official Visit to University of Arizona
    - Photographs of the ground breaking ceremony for the U of A Science building, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 16: Orbiter
    - 1966-1969 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 17: Planetary and Interplanetary Science Subcommittee
    - 1960-1962 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 18: Planetology Subcommittee
    - 1960-1962 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - 1963 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 19: Ranger
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (1) (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (2) (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Ranger VI Block 3, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Ranger VII, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Ranger VII Report Draft, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Ranger VII Report Photography/Diagrams, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Ranger VII Final Report, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Ranger VII clean-up frames, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Ranger VII First analysis of data, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ranger VII early reports and photographs, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ranger VII interpretation of the Ranger records, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Ranger VIII-IX,Lunar results, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Ranger VIII-IX, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Ranger VIII – IX Interpretation of the Ranger Records, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Ranger VIII Original Release Set Photographs, February 2, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Ranger IX Bearing Strength of Alphonsus Crater, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Ranger Atlas, 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Ranger History, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Ranger Notes, [1964] (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Ranger Program TV Picture, 1960-1964 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 20: Space Flight Earth Photographs
    - 1962-1971 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 21: Space Program
    - 1961 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - 1965 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 22: Space Research
    - 1970-1973 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 23: Space Sciences Building/University of Arizona
    - Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Committee, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Committee, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Proposal for a Space Sciences Center, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Space Sciences Building Dedication and Symposium on the Lunar Surface, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Space Science Building Photographs of the Dedication, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - NASA visiting committee, February 15, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 24: Space Science Steering Committee
    - 1960 (binder) (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 25: Surveyor
    - 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - 1962 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - 1963 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - 1966 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - 1967 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - 1968-1973 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 26: Tiros Weather Satellite
    - 1960-1966 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 27: Viking Project
    - 1954-1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 28: Voyager Mission to Mars
    - 1965 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Series: VIII: National Science Foundation, 1959-1973.
  - 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - 1954-1962 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 1963-1967 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 1968-1973 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Series: IX: Publication Files. This series is arranged alphabetically. It is a record of Dr. Kuiper’s writing career. This subgroup is divided into 6 series: Solar System. Stars and Stellar Systems, articles, lectures, papers. Atlases. Book Chapters. Notes, 1944-1974.
  - Subseries 1: Solar System, 1951-1966
    - Sub-subseries 1: Volume 1: The Sun
      - Chapter 6 (1), undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 6 (2), undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Chapter 6 (3), undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 6 (4), undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 6 - figures, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 9 (1), undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Chapter 9 (2), undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Volume 2: The Earth as a Planet
      - Figures from chapters 9 and 12, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Volume 3: Planets and satellites
      - Chapter 1, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Chapter 4, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 5, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 8 (1), undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 8 (2), undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 11, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 13, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 14, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 16, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 18, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Volume 4: The moon, meteorites, and comets
      - Chapter 3, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 16, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 17, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 18, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Chapter 19, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Chapter 21, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - The Moon, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Reviews, 1951-1955, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 17,)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Correspondence from editors and authors
      - Alexander, Mary, 1951-1960 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Babcock Harold D., 1952-1962 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Bates, D.R., 1953-1954 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Beals, C.S., 1939-1963 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Brower, Dirk, 1954-1961 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Daniels, Glenn, 1953-1954 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Evans, John W., 1953-1961 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Fagerstrom, Irene E., 1953-1961 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Finsen, W.S., 1955-1966 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - Goetz, John B., 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - Goldberg, Leo, 1952-1966 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - Hagihara Y., 1950-1962 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Harrison, Brown, 1950-1961 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Hemens, Rollin D., 1950-1957 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Herget, Paul, 1950-1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Herzberg, Gerhard, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Holliday, Cylde, 1950-1954 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Hutchinson, G.E., 1950-1954 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Jefferys, Harold, 1950-1954 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Jones, Harold Spence, 1950-1955 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Kiepenheuer, K.O., 1953-1966 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - King, Jean I., 1952-1957 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Krinov, E.L., 1957-1961 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Kuiper, Gerard P., 1961-1963 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Jacchia, Luigi, 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Larimer, John W., 1968 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Lenham, Allan P., 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Lipskiy, Y.M., 1961-1966 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Mason, Brian, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Mayer, Cornell H., 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Mikhailoy, A.A., 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Millman, Peter M., 1956-1964 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Minnaert, Marcel, 1951-1966 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Mohler, O.C., 1950-1952 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Nagy, Bartholomew, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Nicolet, M., 1952-1954 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Niminger, H.H., 1955-1966 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Oort, J.H., 1950-1964 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Paetzold, H.K., 1956-1962 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Pawsey, J. L., 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Pettit, Edison, 1950-1966 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Porter, J.G., 1961-1966 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Roberts, W.O., 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Roemer, Elizabeth, 1960-1963 (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - Rottenberg, J.A., 1961-1966 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - Russell, H.N., 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Shoemaker, E.M, 1959-1963 (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - Shugg, Roger W., 1961-1963 (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - Simpson, J.A., 1953-1966 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Sinton, William M., 1959-1966 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - Sitterly, Charlotte Moore, 1951-1961 (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - Sverdrup, H.U., 1950-1954 (Box 32, Folder 41)
      - Swings, Pol, 1952-1962 (Box 32, Folder 42)
      - Tombaugh, C.W., 1953-1966 (Box 32, Folder 43)
      - Tousey, R., 1950-1966 (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - Van De Hulst, Henk C., 1952-1967 (Box 32, Folder 45)
      - Vladimir, Reichl L., 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 46)
      - Wexler, Harry, 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 47)
      - Whipple, Fred, 1954-1962 (Box 32, Folder 48)
      - Wild, J.P., 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 49)
      - Wildt, Rupert, 1950-1961 (Box 32, Folder 50)
      - Wilson, J.T., 1950-1961 (Box 32, Folder 51)
      - Woods, J.A., 1961-1966 (Box 32, Folder 52)
      - Wright, Helen, 1961-1966 (Box 32, Folder 53)
      - Wurm, K., 1950-1966 (Box 32, Folder 54)
      - A - G (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - H - M (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - N - Z (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2: Stars and Stellar Systems, 1954-1968
    - Sub-subseries 1: Volumes 1-9
      - Preface to Series, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Volume 1 - Telescopes, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Volume 2 - Astronomical techniques, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Volume 3 - Basic astronomical data, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Volume 4 - Clusters and binaries, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Volume 5 - Galactic structure, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Volume 6 - Stellar atmospheres, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Volume 7 - Nebulae and interstellar matter, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Volume 8 - Stellar structure, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Volume 9 - Galaxies and the universe, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Reviews
      - [1961-1961] (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Correspondence from editors and authors
      - Alexander, Mary, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Aller, Lawerance, 1955-1963 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Aller, Lawrence, 1964-1967 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Babcock, Horace, 1954-1962 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Bamford, Dotha, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Bashkin, Stanley, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Blaauw, Adriaan, 1955-1967 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Bolton, J.G., 1957-1960 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Bowen, Ira. S., 1954-1960 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Boyer, Edna, 1956-1960 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Czyzak, Stanely, 1964-1966 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Danjon, A, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Davis, Leverett, Jr., 1960-1968 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - Dietz,Robert, 1960-1963 (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Dollfus, Audouin, 1957-1962 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Drake, F.D., 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - Flack, Margaret, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - Goetz, John B., 1960-1965 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - Goldberg Leo, 1956-1960 (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - Greenburg, J. Mayo, 1961-1967 (Box 33, Folder 34)
      - Greenstien, Jess L., 1954-1964 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Haro, Guillermo, 1964-1968 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Hemen, Rollin D., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Hiltner, W.A., 1956-1962 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Johnson, Hugh M., 1960-1968 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Johnson, J.R., 1962-1963 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Kerr, F.J., 1962-1967 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Kopal, Z., 1960-1963 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Kuiper, Gerard P., 1956-1969 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Ledoux, P., 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Liller, William, 1961-1967 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Markowitz, William, 1954-1960 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - McLanghlin, D.B., 1954-1960 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Meinel, A.B., 1958-1960 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Minkowski, Rudolph, 1965-1960 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Mohler, Orren D., 1956-1962 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Narita, George, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Parker, Eugene N., 1964-1968 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Reichl, Vladimir L., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Richter, Anders, 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Sandage, Allan, 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Schmidt, Maarten, 1958-1964 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Sears, Dick, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Spitzer, Lyman Jr., 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Stock, Jurgen, 1959-1962 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Strand, KAa, 1956-1968 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Struve, Otto, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Sutherland, Dorothy, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Upton, E.K.L., 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Weaver, Harold, 1955-1966 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Wheatley, Sue, 1964-1966 (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Wheatley, Sue, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Wood,Frank Bradshaw, 1954-1962 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - Young, Bruce, 1954-1962 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - Zwicky, F., 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - A - C (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - D - K (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - L - P (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - R - Z (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 3: Articles, talks, lectures, papers., 1936-1974
    - 10 years of astronomical observation at McDonald observatory, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Abundances of the elements, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Adventures of the mind on the moon, 1958-1961 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Asteroid light curves, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Asteroids, 1956, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Asteroids and Meteorites, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - The Asteroids as the sources of the meteorites, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Asteroids – computations, 1949-1956 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Astronomy and astrophysics in Hawaii, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Astrophysical topics/Purdue lectures, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - The Atmosphere and cloud layer of Venus, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Atmosphere of the earth and planets, 1948-1949 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Atmosphere of the earth and planets, 1950-1952; 1957 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Atmosphere of the earth and planets, 2nd edition, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Binary Stars, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Cloudcroft, New Mexico summer lecture series, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Comets and the dissipation of the solar nebula, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Comments on the future, undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - The Composition of Saturn's rings, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Development of the lunar surface, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Diameters of planets and satellites, 1953-1955 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Dimensions of contact surfaces in close binaries, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Does the earth have a second satellite, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Dwarf stars, [1947] (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Effects of a National Space Program on Universities, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - An Emission produced by single stars, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Empirical mass luminosity relation, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Environment of the moon and the planets, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Epsilon Aurigae, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Extraterrestrial life, panel, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Extraterrestrial life, panel, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - The Formation of the planets, part 2 and 3, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Future observational work on double stars, [1952] (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - German astronomy during the war, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Hertzsprung–Russell diagram/abstract, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - High and low velocity stars, [1944-1947] (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - High resolution planetary observation, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Identification of the Venus cloud layers, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Impressions of the mapping science laboratory, undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Infrared and radio discussion report, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Infrared equipment, 1946-1947 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Infrared spectra of planets and cool stars, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Interpretation of the Jupiter red spot, 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Interpretation of lunar probe data, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Is there life on Mars?, 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - The Lunar and Planetary Laboratory, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - A Lunar evening with Dr. Kuiper, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Lunar explorations, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Lunar rock - Maanstenen, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Lunar studies, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - The Lunar surface and the U.S. Ranger Program, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Lunar surface features, and internal development of the moon, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Micrometer measurements of double stars, abstract only, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - The Moon, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - The Moon and earth, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - The Moon and its origin, November 12, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Nature of the lunar surface, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Nature of the lunar surface, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - The Nearest stars, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Notes on 10 year program on planetary astronomy, undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Observations of planetary surface detail, undated (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Observing with the 200” Hale telescope, not published, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - On the interpretation of Lyrae and other close binaries, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - On the nature of the Venus clouds, November 1970 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - On the need for a ground-based lunar and planetary observatory, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - On the need for a ground-based lunar and planetary observatory, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - On the origin of binary stars, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - On the origin of the satellites and the Trojans, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - On the origin of the solar system, 1948–1953 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - On the origin of the solar system, October 1950 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - On the origin of the solar system - NAS, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - On the origin of the solar system, April 1952 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - On the origin of the solar system, June 1953 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - On the origin of the solar system, [1953] (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - On the origin of the solar system computations, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - On the origin of the solar system - part 1, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - On the origin of the solar system - part 2, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - On the Origin of the earth and planets, 1956-1960 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Origin of the moon and planets - abstract only, February 1973 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Paradox/Theory of the solar system, 1949-1967 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Percentage of clear weather at 18 selected sights, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Photometric records of planetary and stellar spectra, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Photometric studies of asteroids, 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Physical properties of planets and satellites, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Physics of planets and satellites, [1963] (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Pioneer Project, comments, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - The planet mars, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Planetary and satellite atmosphere, 1949-1951 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Planetary Atmosphere, 1947-1958 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Planets and satellites, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Planets, satellites and comets, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - The Planets - filmstrip script, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Planets, life?, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Planets, satellites and comets, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Problems in planetary physics, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Provisional Analysis of Russian Luna - 9 pictures, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Pseudo Science and its dangers, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Recent results on the sun, moon and planets - Dryden lecture, January 20,1969 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Reconnaissance of the infrared stellar spectra, undated (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Religion and the scientist, [1951] (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Samples of infrared stellar spectra, undated (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Statistics of asteroids, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Stellar temperatures, 1939-1940 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - The Story of B Lyrae, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Studies of the planet Jupiter at the Lunar and Planetary Laboratory, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Summary of infrared observations on stars and planets, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - The Surface of the moon, 1961-1966 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - The Surface structure and history of the moon, May 16, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Survey of Asteroids, 1952-1962 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Tale of two planets, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified flying objects, April 9, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - The United States Ranger program results of the moon, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - The United States space program, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - The United States space flights, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Venus, [1956] (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Venus atmosphere, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Voice of America - The Lunar surface, Uranus and Neptune, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Voyage to the planets, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - White dwarfs, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - White dwarfs, sub dwarfs and main sequence, 1941 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, Presentations - talks/lectures, undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 4: Atlases, 1953-1974
    - Consolidated Lunar Atlas - Supplement 3, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - NASA – Arizona Atlas of the Infrared Solar Spectrum, 1968; 1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Orthographic Atlas of the Moon Supplement - 1, 1957-1960 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Orthographic Atlas of the Moon Supplement - 2, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Photographic Lunar Atlas, 1953-1960 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Rectified Lunar Atlas Supplement - 2, undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Subseries 5: Book Chapters, 1944-1965
    - Sub-subseries 1: By publication title
      - Advances in Earth Science, 1963-1965 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - American Peoples Encyclopedia, 1954–1959 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Atmosphere of the Earth and Planets, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Compton's Encyclopedia, 1971-1963 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1956-1960 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - McGraw Hill Encyclopedia of Science, 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Planet Earth, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Science and scientists in the Indies, 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Vistas in astronautics - Chapter 12, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Sub-subseries 2: By title of chapter - publication title unknown.
      - Spectra and dimensions of dwarf stars, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)